Atlantic States Legal Foundation; Records apap311
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Projects, 1967-2009; Undated; 1; 118.92 cubic ft.
  - Northeast, 1970-2009; Undated; 1.2
    - New York - American Packaging Corp. Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - New York - American Packaging Corp. Court Documents, 1992-1994 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - New York - American Packaging Corp. Pollution Prevention Plan, 1994 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - New York - American Pipe & Plastic Inc. Permit and Air Pollution Data list, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - New York - AMF Bowling Inc. Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - New York - AMF Bowling Inc. Court Documents, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 38)
    - New York - AMF Bowling Inc. Pollution Prevention/Toxics Use Reduction Plan, 1994 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 1-2)
    - New York - AMF Bowling Inc. Pollution Prevention/Toxics Use Reduction Plan Executive Summary, 1994 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - AMF Bowling Inc. Pollution Prevention/Toxics Use Reduction Plan Progress Reports, 1994-1997 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - AMF Bowling Inc. Pollution Prevention/Toxics Use Reduction Plan Progress Reports, 1989-1990; 1992; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Anaren Microwave Inc. Correspondence, Notes, Generator Annual Report, and Waste Manifest, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Anheuser-Busch Inc. Correspondence and Permit, 1987-1990 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Applied Design Co. Generator Annual Report, 1988 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - APV/Crepaco Inc. Correspondence, Court Document, and Notes, 1990 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Arcata Graphics Buffalo, Inc. Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Arcata Graphics Buffalo, Inc. Court Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Arcata Graphics Buffalo, Inc. DMRs, Waste Manifest, 1987; 1992-1993 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Arcata Graphics Buffalo, Inc. Waste Manifest Reduction System Design Report, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Archer Daniels Midland Co. and Clinton Processing Co. Outfall Violations, Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Archer Daniels Midland Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1982-1989; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Archer Daniels Midland Co. Court Documents, 1984-1986 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 16-17)
    - New York - Archer Daniels Midland Co. Court Documents Plaintiff Brief, 1988 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 18-19)
    - New York - Archer Daniels Midland Co. Court Documents, 1988-1992; 1994 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 20-21)
    - New York - Archer Daniels Midland Co. Evaluation of Lack of Compliance with NPDES Permit, 1989 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Aro Corp. Chemical Inventory, Generator Annual Report, Waste Manifest and Permit Application, 1987-1990 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Aro Corp. Correspondence, Generator Annual Report, Air Pollution Data list, 1988-1990 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Aro Corp. Correspondence, Court Documents and Notes, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Atlantic Design Co. Generator Annual Report, Air Pollution Data list, 1988-1990 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Auburn, City of, Correspondence and Notes, 1986; 1987 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Auburn, City of, Court Documents, 1974; 1989 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Auburn, City of, Permit and DMRs, 1981; 1985-1987 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Auto Radiator Sales Inc. Correspondence, 1993-1997; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - New York - Auto Radiator Sales Inc. Court Documents, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - New York - Auto Radiator Sales Inc. Pollution Prevention/Toxic Use Reduction Program, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - New York - Aqua Clear Industries, Inc. Correspondence, Court Documents, Notes, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - New York - Basco Division Correspondence and Court Document, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - New York - Basco Division Material Safety Data, Chemical Description, EPA Forms, 1985; 1989-1990 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - New York - Bates Troy Laundry Correspondence, Generator Annual Report, 1988; 1990 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - New York - BASF Wyandotte Corp. Correspondence, Notes, 1989 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - New York - BASF Wyandotte Corp. Summary of Pretreatment Analysis and Wastewater Inception and Treatment Contract, 1989 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 38)
    - New York - Bell Aerospace Textron Waste Manifest and Generator Annual Report, 1981-1988 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Bendix Corp. Motor components Piv. Discharge Notes, 1978-1981; Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Bennett Manufacturing Co. Inc. Correspondence and Notes, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Bennett Manufacturing Co. Inc. Court Documents, 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Bennett Manufacturing Co. Inc. Evaluation of Chemical Utilization, Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Bennett Manufacturing Co. Inc. Generator Annual Reports, EPA Forms, and Waste Manifests, 1988-1990 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Bethlehem Steel Corp. Assessment of Public Comments, 1991 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Bethlehem Steel Corp. Bioconcentration and Remobilization of Trace Metals and Polychlorinated Biphenyls in Zebra Mussels, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Bethlehem Steel Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1985; 1988-1989; 1991-1992 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Bethlehem Steel Corp. Court Documents, 1984; 1992 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Bethlehem Steel Corp. Permit and DMR, 1988-1989 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Bethlehem Steel Corp. SPDES Permit Reapplication, 1989 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 12-13)
    - New York - BDT Inc. Generator Annual Report, 1987 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Binghamton, City of, Correspondence, Notes, Court Documents, and Permit, 1987; 1990-1992; Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Binghamton, Johnson City, Correspondence and Billing, 1988; 1990-1992 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Binghamton, Johnson City, Court Documents, 1988; 1991-1992 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Binghamton, Johnson City Joint Sewage Board, 1986-1987 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Binghamton, Johnson City Permit and Monthly Averages, 1984; 1990 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Binghamton, Johnson City Standing, 1991 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Bison Bag Generator Annual Report, Waste Manifest, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Black River Basin Board of Hudson River-Black River Regulating District, Economic Feasibility Study, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Black River Basin Correspondence and Notes, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Black River Basin Court Documents, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Black River Basin Gorge Resource Council Economic Potential of the Lower Black River, Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Black River Basin, National Association for State River Conservation Programs Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Blasdell, Village of, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Borden, Inc. Correspondence and Notes, 1982; Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Aerobic Biological Treatment Tests, Undated (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Air Pollution Source Management, 1992 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Annual Report, 1988 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Blueprints, 1990 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 32-33)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Consent Decree, 1992 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Consent Decree Drafts and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 7 (1-Projects), Folder 35-37)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Contract Documents Sewer Consolidation Project, 1990 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 1-2)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Correspondence, 1989 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 4-5)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Correspondence, 1990 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Correspondence, 1991 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Correspondence, 1992 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Correspondence, 1993 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Court Documents, 1989 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Court Documents, 1990 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 13-14)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Court Documents, 1991 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Court Documents, 1992 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Court Documents, 1995 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. DMR Research Sheet and Industrial Waste Monitoring, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. EPA Form Rs, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. "Free Ammonia & Toxicity Criteria in a Polluted Urban Lake", 1990 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Memorandum of Understanding, Undated (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Metropolitan Syracuse Wastewater Treatment Plant, 1989 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Multimedia Order on Consent, Undated (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Newsclippings, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Notes, 1989-1991 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 25-26)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Permits, 1985; 1989; 1992 (Box 8 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. "Protecting Health Preserving the Environment", Undated (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. "Report on Environmental Progress", 1993 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Self Monitoring Reports, 1990 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Self Monitoring Reports, 1991 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Self Monitoring Reports, 1992 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 5-7)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Self Monitoring Reports, 1993 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Spill Prevention Control, 1987 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Quarterly Progress Reports, 1992 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Third Quarterly Report, "The Merger", 1989 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Unidentified Attachments, 1989 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Study Final Report, January, 1994 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Study Final Report, February, 1994 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Air Quality and Health Report Impact Analysis, 1993 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Air Quality and Health Report Impact Analysis, 1994 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Digester Gas and Broiler System Evaluation, October, 1993 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Digester Gas and Broiler System Evaluation, November, 1993 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Mass Balance Analysis, 1993 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 19-20)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Mass Balance Analysis, 1994 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Mass Balance Analysis, Appendices A-E, 1994 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Mass Balance Analysis, Appendix F, 1994 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 23-24)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Mass Balance Analysis, Appendices G-L, 1994 (Box 9 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Mass Balance Analysis, Appendices G-L, 1994 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Mass Balance Analysis, Appendix M, 1994 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Wastewater/Sludge Impact Analyses, 1993 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 3-4)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Metro STP Wastewater/Sludge Impact Analyses, 1994 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Study Technical Evaluation of Local Discharge Limits, January, 1994 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Volatile Compounds Study Technical Evaluation of Local Discharge Limits, February, 1994 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Wastewater Pretreatment Study Task 3, 1993 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 8-12)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Wastewater Pretreatment Study Vol. 1 Task 1, 1992 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Wastewater Pretreatment Study Vol. II Appendix B.1-1992 Analytical Data Package (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 14-15)
    - New York - Bristol-Myers Squibb Co. Wastewater Pretreatment Study Vol. II Appendix B.2-1992 Analytical Data Package (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 16-17)
    - New York - Broome County, Correspondence and Notes, 1990; Undated (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Broome County, List of Facilities, 1987-1990 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Browner, Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Browner, Court Documents, 1995-1996 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Bruce Babbitt, Court Documents, 2000 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Bruce Babbitt, Correspondence, 1991-2001; 2003 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Bruce Babbitt, Legal Defense, 1999 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Bruce Babbitt, Motion to Dismiss, 1999-2000 (Box 10 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Bruce Babbitt, Procedural, 1999-2000; 2009 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Bruce Babbitt, Second Circuit Appeal Procedural, 2001 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Bruce Babbitt, Summons, 1999 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Bruce Babbitt, Summons, Complaint and Memorandum of Law, 1999 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - BTL Inc. Waste Manifest, 1987 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Buckingham Manufacturing Co. Inc. Air Pollution Data List, 1990 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Buffalo Envelope Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1989-1995; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Buffalo Envelope Co. Court Documents, 1989-1990 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Buffalo Envelope Co. Court Documents, 1991 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Buffalo Envelope Co. Court Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Buffalo Envelope Co. Court Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Buffalo Envelope Co. EPA Forms, Waste Manifest, Chemical Descriptions, 1987-1990 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Buffalo Envelope Co. EPA Reports, 1988; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Buffalo Envelope Co. Toxic Use Reduction Assessment, 1993 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Buffalo Metal Furnishings Co. Generator Annual Report, Waste Manifest, Notes, 1988-1990 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Buffalo Sewer Authority Correspondence, Notes and List of Permits, 1989-1990 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Calspian Corp. ERA Form, 1989 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Camden Wire Co. Inc. Correspondence, Permit, Notes, 1987; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Canandaigua Water Park, Correspondence, 2000 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Canandaigua Water Park, Newsclippings, 2000 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Case Finding Research Notes and Correspondence, 1981-1984; 1986; 1988-1993; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Cases in Process Correspondence and Notes, 1983-1987; 1990-1993; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Cases Not Recommended Correspondence and Notes, 1980; 1988; 1990-1993; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Central Hudson Gas & Electric Co. Correspondence, Notes, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Central Hudson Gas & Electric Co. Court Documents, 1984-1985; Undated; 2004 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Central Hudson Gas & Electric Co. DMR, 1975-1980; 1985-1986 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Chagrin Fibers Inc. Correspondence, Court Documents, Notes, DMR, 1976; 1983-1985 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Champion International Corp. Correspondence and Permit, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Chem Central Corp. Generator Annual Report, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Chemical Leaman Tank Lines Inc. Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 30-31)
    - New York - Chemical Leaman Tank Lines Inc. Court Documents, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - New York - Chemical Leaman Tank Lines Inc. Permit and Discharge Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - New York - Chemical Leaman Tank Lines Inc. Waste, Undated (Box 11 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - New York - Chenango Industries Inc. Chemical Description, Generator Annual Report, Air Pollution Data list, EPA Forms, 1987-1990 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Chenango Industries Inc. Correspondence and Notes, 1987-1996; Undated (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 2-3)
    - New York - Chenango Industries Inc. Court Documents, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Chenango Industries Inc. Pollution Prevention Plan, 1993 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Chenango Industries Inc. Statement of Operation, 1988-1990 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Chenango Industries Inc. Summary of Reviewed Questionnaire, 1982 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Cibro Petroleum Products Inc. Permit, 1989 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Clardon Swimming Pool Service and Excavation Correspondence and Notes, 1987; 1991; Undated (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - CMP Industrial Inc. Correspondence, Permit, Generator Annual Report, 1985; 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Coca-Cola Bottling Co. of New York Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1990-1994; 1996 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Court Documents, 1990 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Court Documents, 1991 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Court Documents, 1992 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 15-16)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Court Documents, 1993 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Court Documents Defendants Answers, 1990 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 18-19)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Court Documents Defendant's Supplemental Answers, 1991 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 20-24)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Financial Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Colonial Tanning Corp. Permits, 1989-1990 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Colonie Wood Treating & Staining Corp. Correspondence, Court Documents, 1992-1994 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Colonie Wood Treating & Staining Corp. EPA Forms, Chemical Descriptions, 1992-1994 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Colonie Wood Treating & Staining Corp. Pollution Prevention Assessment Summary Report, 1993 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Colorforms, Inc. Correspondence, Generator Annual Report, Waste Manifest, 1987-1990 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - New York - Colt Industries Correspondence and Court Documents, 1984; 1985 (Box 12 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - New York - Com Cir Tek Inc. Correspondence and Notes, 1988-1992; Undated (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Com Cir Tek Inc. Court Documents, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Com Cir Tek Inc. Environmental Compliance Program, 1987 (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Com Cir Tek Inc. EPA Permit Forms, Generator Annual Report, and Waste Manifest, 1987-1993 (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Com Cir Tek Inc. Pollution Prevention Plan, 1992 (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Com Cir Tek Inc. Sample Analytical Results, 1987-1993 (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Comments on New York Power Authority's Proposal SEQRA Regulation, 1995 (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Community Right to Know Newsclipping, Articles, and Press Release, 1983; 1990; Undated (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Consolidated Rail Corp., Friends of the Earth, Plaintiff Correspondence and Note, 1979; 1982-1987; Undated (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Consolidated Rail Corp., Friends of the Earth, Plaintiff Court Documents, 1979; 1982-1983; Undated (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Consolidated Rail Corp., Friends of the Earth, Plaintiff Court Documents, 1984 (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 11-12)
    - New York - Consolidated Rail Corp., Friends of the Earth, Plaintiff Court Documents, 1985 (Box 13 (1-Projects), Folder 13)